linclik.com 2016-12-03

# Privacy Policy

### Bucharest, Romania July 10, 2016 These terms are subject to change.

Our terms of use and privacy policy offers a detailed explanation regarding your personal data provided to us or any data we may collect from you. This privacy policy is updated from time to time; therefore, it should be reviewed from time to time. 

###  1\. Information obtained

Data can be collected and processed during the operations of our website. The following are ways we can carry out these actions: 1.1 Data collected about your visit (s) on our website and the resources used. The following is included and not limited to: location data, weblogs, traffic data, and any other communication information. 1.2 Any way you filled out on our site allows us to collect data such as registration information or complete a purchase. 1.3 If for any reason you communicate with our personnel or site we may collect information. 

###  2\. Use of Cookies

There are cases where we may use cookies to collect information about our services in a mathematical collection for our website and our advertisers. All information collected will not have any identifying information. This is statistical data about our visitors and how they have used our site. No personal data will be shared that could identify him. We may collect information about your use of common Internet with a cookie file. When used, cookies are downloaded to your computer automatically. The cookie is stored on the hard drive, with transferred information. The data collected by the cookie helps us improve our website and any services provided to you. Your browser has the ability to reject cookies. This is done by setting your browser options to reject all cookies. Note: if you do reject the download of cookies, some aspects of our site may not work or allow access. Our advertisers may download cookies to which we have no control. If used, these cookies are downloaded by clicking on an advertisement on our website. 

###  3\. Our use of your information

The stored or collected regarding you helps us improve and offer services you need information. The following list contains how we might use your data: 3.1 Any request we make of our site or personnel allows us to use the information you provided in connection with the goods or services we have. We may also send information about products or services that might interest you, provided that consent has been received. 3.2 Contract Commitments: To meet any commitment we make to you. 3.3 Changes or improvements to the site can justify the use of their information regarding the notification of such changes. 3.4 An existing customer may be contacted regarding products and services related to the sale of any previous article that has placed on our site. 3.5 We may use data or allow third parties to use information that is not related to the goods or services that might be interested. We or third parties contact you only if consent has been provided by you at any time, based on the information we collected. 3.6 Any new customer can only be contacted by us or by third parties if consent has been offered via our site. We only send communications you have consented. 3.7 Anyone who does not want to consent to our use third party site or have the opportunity to decline. Once we receive your consent for concealment we will remove your data from any third party mail or communications. 3.8 None of the information collected about you will offer identifiable characteristics. The shared information to a third party is only statistical. We will not reveal who you are, only mathematical information about our visitors is. 

###  4\. Personal Data Storage

4.1 Locations outside the European Economic Area can be used for transferring data we collect about you. These sites are data for storage or processing of your information. The information we share outside the European Economic Area may be shared with staff based on the processing and storage of such data. You can include processes such as processing a payment or offering support to their needs service or product. Processing or storage of personal information may work for our suppliers outside the European Economic Area. By submitting your data you use you have accepted this transfer and data storage. We take all reasonable measures to ensure the security of their personal data in accordance with this privacy policy. 4.2 Information to be provided is stored on secure servers. transaction data is encrypted for security. 4.3 You should understand data via online transmission is not completely secure. We can not guarantee the full protection and data security, only that we take all reasonable measures to protect information sent to us electronically. Transmission of data by you is at your own risk. In your case you can give you access to sections of our site that require a password. You are responsible for the security and confidentiality of passwords. 

###  5\. Information

5.1 Sometimes we may disclose personal information to people in our group. This can include subsidiaries, holding companies, or any other subsidiaries involved in our business, if applicable. 5.2 Third Party disclosure may occur for the following reasons: 5.2.1 The sale of any or all of our business to a third party may result in sharing your information. 5.2.2 At any time when we are legally required to we may disclose information about you and your visits to our sites. 5.2.3 To prevent fraud and help in fraud protection in order to reduce credit risk, we may disclose information. 

###  6\. Third Party Links

third party links may be discovered on our site. These third party links have their own privacy policy, which you agree to when you click on the link. We are not responsible nor do we accept responsibility for third party links. Our liability covers us only on our site, and therefore not responsible for third party links as we have no control over them. 

###  7\. Information

We can not retain the data we collect about you, according to the Data Protection Act 1998. This act provides access to any information we have about you. If you want to access data about the collection you please pay the fee? 10. The fee covers the costs to process your application and get the data for you. Please use the contact details below to formulate requests for access to data. 

###  8\. Contacting Us

Please feel free to contact us with queries, requests or comments you may have about our privacy policy ..
